♪ Move your feet
and grab your seat ♪
♪ 移动你的脚
坐下来♪
♪ It's "The Sir Urchin
and Snail Fail Show" ♪
♪ 这是“顽童先生”
和蜗牛失败秀”♪
both: It's on!
两人：开始了！
Ah!
啊!
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
- Pardon me!
- Excuse me!
- 请原谅我！
- 打扰一下！
It's "The Sir Urchin
and Snail Fail Show."
这是“顽童爵士
和蜗牛失败秀。”
Hmph.
哼。
Hmm.
唔。
Woe is me.
祸哉是我。
My priceless works of art need
to be dusted!
我的无价艺术作品需要
去除尘！
Oh, Snail Fail!
哦，蜗牛失败！
Whoa!
哇！
Yes, sir, Sir Urchin, sir!
是的，先生，顽童先生，先生！
Dust my art!
灰尘我的艺术！
Very good, Sir Urchin, sir.
非常好，顽童先生，先生。
Ah, you dust divinely.
啊，你灰尘神圣。
Now dust the back!
现在除尘背面！
Uh, v-v-very good,
Sir Urchin, sir.
呃，非常好，
乌尔钦先生，先生。
Wah.
哇。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
哇、哇、哇、哇、哇！
Oh.
哦。
Why, you!
为什么，你！
What I do?
我做什么？
Whoa, dainty, dainty, dainty!
哇，好吃，好吃，好吃！
- Ah!
- Hm?
- 啊！
- 嗯？
Why, you!
为什么，你！
What I do?
我做什么？
Why, you!
为什么，你！
What I do?
我做什么？
Ah!
啊!
Why, you!
为什么，你！
Why you, indeed.
为什么是你，确实。
Huh?
Whoa, whoa!
啊？
哇哦！
Huh?
啊？
Why not any of us?
为什么我们任何人都不能呢？
If the nature
of the universe is random,
如果大自然
宇宙是随机的，
would not misfortune
find us all equally?
不会遭遇不幸
发现我们所有人都是平等的吗？
And yet, it does not.
然而，事实并非如此。
Perhaps you should stop
asking, "Why you?"
也许你应该停下来
问：“为什么是你？”
and start asking, "Why me?"
并开始问：“为什么是我？”
That's not the line.
那不是那条线。
Why did you stop hitting me?
你为什么不再打我了？
I want the audience to know
that I am a real thespian
我想让观众知道
我是一个真正的演员
and not just
some bumbling buffoon.
不仅仅是
一些笨手笨脚的小丑。
Well, you wanna be
a serious actor?
好吧，你想成为
一个严肃的演员？
Nobody's stopping you!
没人能阻止你！
Exit stage left!
离开舞台！
My pleasure!
我的荣幸！
I quit!
我不干了！
Why, you--
为什么，你——
It's no joke, Patrick.
这不是玩笑，帕特里克。
Our favorite comedy team
just broke up on live TV!
我们最喜欢的喜剧团队
刚刚在电视直播中分手！
♪ Move your feet
and grab your seat ♪
♪ 移动你的脚
并坐下来♪
both: ♪ It's "The Sir Urchin
and Snail Fail Show" ♪
两者：♪ 这是“顽童先生
和蜗牛失败表演”♪
Patrick, as devoted fans,
帕特里克作为忠实粉丝，
it's our duty to convince
our two idols
我们有责任说服
我们的两个偶像
to get back together.
复合。
The future of comedy
depends on it.
喜剧的未来
取决于它。
I'm in!
我进来了！
We'll have to split up.
我们得分手了。
Aw, I was just getting comfy.
噢，我刚刚变得舒服了。
I'll go find Snail Fail,
我会去找蜗牛失败，
and you track down Sir Urchin.
然后你找到了顽童爵士。
Good luck.
祝你好运。
Booyah!
嘘！
Whoo!
呼！
Taxi!
出租车！
Where to, Mac?
去哪儿，麦克？
Take me
to Sir Urchin's house.
带我去
去乌尔钦爵士的家。
Sir Urchin?
乌金先生？
Yeah, Sir Urchin!
是啊，顽童先生！
You know, the guy that goes...
你知道，那个走的人...
"Why, you!"
“怎么，你！”
He's so funny.
他真有趣。
Oh, you mean like this?
哦，你是说像这样吗？
Why, you!
为什么，你！
I'm Sir Urchin.
我是乌尔钦爵士。
Ay-yah!
哎呀！
Sir Urchin?
乌金先生？
Why are you driving a taxi?
你为什么开出租车？
My partner and I broke up
我和我的伴侣分手了
five minutes ago,
and since then,
五分钟前，
从那时起，
times have been tough.
日子过得很艰难。
Mm.
毫米。
You guys were so funny
back then!
你们真是太有趣了
那时！
What I do?
我做什么？
Say, Mac, how would you like
说吧，Mac，你想要什么？
to be Snail Fail the Second?
成为第二个蜗牛失败者？
Would I?
我会吗？
Oh?
What is this?
哦？
这是什么？
Huh.
呵呵。
Probably a gift
from one of my adoring fans.
可能是一份礼物
来自我的一位崇拜者。
Close.
I am an adoring fan.
关闭。
我是一个忠实的粉丝。
Ah!
啊!
Doing!
I'm sorry, Mr. Snail Fail.
正在做！
对不起，蜗牛失败先生。
I just wanted to ask
if you and Sir Urchin could
我只是想问
如果你和顽童爵士可以的话
get back together again.
再次聚在一起。
You know,
for your adoring fans.
你知道，
为您的忠实粉丝。
No more low comedy for me.
对我来说，不再有低级喜剧了。
The only way I shall ever
step on a stage again
我唯一能做的就是
再次登上舞台
is as a serious dramatic actor.
是作为一个严肃的戏剧演员。
Now, be gone!
现在，走吧！
Ah!
啊!
Ohh.
I know a stage
哦。
我知道一个舞台
where people would love
to see you act.
人们会喜欢的地方
看你行动。
Hmm.
唔。
Really?
真的吗？
Alas, poor Mackerel,
唉，可怜的鲭鱼，
I knew him, Halibut.
我认识他，大比目鱼。
A fellow of infinite jest.
一个充满无限笑话的家伙。
He hath borne me
on his fishtail
他生了我
在他的鱼尾上
a thousand times.
一千次。
Ow!
噢！
You stink!
你太臭了！
Whoa!
哇！
Ah!
啊!
Maybe we should
call Sir Urchin.
也许我们应该
打电话给顽童爵士。
Never!
绝不！
- Why, you!
- Aah!
- 为什么，你！
- 啊啊！
What I do?
我做什么？
Why, you!
为什么，你！
What I do?
我做什么？
Why, you!
为什么，你！
What I do?
我做什么？
Why, you!
为什么，你！
What me do?
我做什么？
Why, you!
为什么，你！
What me do?
我做什么？
How come nobody's laughing?
怎么没人笑？
Well, you're saying,
"What me do?"
嗯，你是说，
“我做什么？”
instead of, "What I do?"
而不是“我做什么？”
Maybe that's it.
也许就是这样。
Good note.
好注意。
Got it.
知道了。
Why, you!
为什么，你！
Where I go?
我去哪儿？
Nah, that's not it.
不，不是这样。
If only we had a real stage
to perform on.
要是有一个真正的舞台就好了
执行。
If only I had a real stage
to act on.
要是有一个真正的舞台就好了
采取行动。
Extry, extry!
外线，外线！
Big Bikini Bottom
Talent Show tonight
大比基尼泳裤
今晚才艺表演
on a real stage!
在真实的舞台上！
- Huh.
- Hmph.
- 嗯。
- 哼。
both:
两个都：
This might be the break
这可能就是突破点
we've been waiting for!
我们一直在等待！
both: Yay!
两人：耶！
I smell a reunion!
我闻到了重逢的味道！
Welcome to the Bikini Bottom
Talent show!
欢迎来到比基尼泳裤
才艺表演！
Take it away, Bikini Bottom!
把它拿走，比基尼泳裤！
Oh!
哦！
Whoa!
哇！
Look at all those people!
看看那些人！
Doy!
多伊！
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
Is this the line
for the talent show?
这是这条线吗
为了才艺表演？
Agh!
You.
啊啊！
你。
You.
both: Success!
两人：成功！
It's great to see you guys
back together again!
很高兴见到你们
再次聚在一起！
Whoa!
哇！
I am not following
this riffraff onto the stage.
我没有关注
这个痞子上台了。
We shall go first.
我们先走吧。
Shove off, Fakespeare!
滚开，假士比亚！
Me and my new partner, Patrick,
were here first!
我和我的新搭档帕特里克
我们先来的！
Hey!
嘿！
That monocle was priceless!
那单片眼镜是无价的！
Now it's garbage.
现在是垃圾了。
Why, you!
为什么，你！
Agh!
啊啊！
What did I do
to deserve this fate?
我做了什么
值得这样的命运吗？
Why, you!
为什么，你！
Whoa!
哇！
Ugh!
啊!
What have I done?
我做了什么？
Why, you!
为什么，你！
What is it?
它是什么？
Why, you!
为什么，你！
Are you referring to me?
你指的是我吗？
Yah!
啊！
Why, you!
为什么，你！
both: Hm?
两人：嗯？
What I do?
我做什么？
Our act was perfect
the way it was.
我们的表演很完美
本来就是这样。
I should never have
tried to change it.
我不应该有
试图改变它。
Snail Fail, old buddy,
go ahead.
蜗牛失败，老伙计，
继续吧。
Add some serious acting
to our show.
添加一些严肃的表演
到我们的节目。
I just want to get
back together again!
我只想得到
再次聚在一起！
Oh, so do I!
哦，我也一样！
both: Mm.
两人：嗯。
Why, you.
为什么，你。
What I do?
我做什么？
both: Mm.
两人：嗯。
Oh!
Why, us!
哦！
为什么，我们！
Look what we do'd!
看看我们做了什么！
Why, you!
为什么，你！
Alas, poor Mackerel,
唉，可怜的鲭鱼，
I knew him, Sir Urchin.
我认识他，顽童爵士。
A fellow of infinite jest,
一个充满无限笑话的人，
nautical nonsense
be something he wished.
航海废话
成为他所希望的。
Where be your jokes now,
old friend?
现在你的笑话在哪里，
老朋友？
That I may laugh...
好让我笑...
With merriment?
带着欢乐？
Why, you!
为什么，你！
What hath I done?
我做了什么？
They're back
and funnier than ever!
他们回来了
而且比以往任何时候都更有趣！
Thank you, everyone.
谢谢大家。
We would just like to take
a moment to give a shout-out,
我们只想采取
一个值得大声喊叫的时刻，
as the kids say,
to our friends,
正如孩子们所说，
致我们的朋友，
SpongeBob and Patrick.
海绵宝宝和帕特里克。
both: We couldn't have gotten
back together without you guys!
两人：我们不可能得到
没有你们一起回来！
both: Why, you!
两人：为什么，你！
both: What we do?
两人：我们做什么？
Why, you!
为什么，你！
all: Not again!
全体：不再有！
Aah!
啊！